http://www.wrm.org/privacy

Visit / Discover
Plan Your VisitGroup ToursField TripsMuseum Site MapArchivesMuseum StoreCar RosterEventsAbout Us
Railroad HistoryStaffOur Mission and HistoryBlogSupport Us
Make A DonationMembershipVolunteerContact Us
HomePrivacy
Privacy Policy
IntroductionWe at Bay Area Electric Railroad Association are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us.
Bay Area Electric Railroad Association has established this Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information.
Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit Bay Area Electric Railroad Association's Web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself.
If you choose to provide us with your Personal Information on the Web, we may transfer that Information within Bay Area Electric Railroad Association or to Bay Area Electric Railroad Association's third-party service providers, across borders, and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world.
Bay Area Electric Railroad Association strives to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, Bay Area Electric Railroad Association intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this Online Privacy Policy even if, in connection with the above, we transfer your Personal Information from your country to countries that may not require an "adequate" level of protection for your Personal Information. In other words, our goal is to provide protection for your Personal Information no matter where that Personal Information is collected, transferred, or retained.
Cookies and Other Tracking TechnologiesSome of our Web pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Web site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.
You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the Web site.
Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Web site and your Web experience. We may also analyze information that does not contain Personal Information for trends and statistics.Website AnalyticsTo improve your experience on our site, we may use 'cookies'. Cookies are an industry standard and most major websites use them. A cookie is a small text file that our site may place on your computer as a tool to remember your preferences. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.
Our website may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these or other sites. When you go to other websites from this site, we advise you to be aware and read their privacy policies.
Our website uses Google Analytics, a service which transmits website traffic data to Google servers. Google Analytics does not identify individual users or associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. We use reports provided by Google Analytics to help us understand website traffic and webpage usage.
By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner described in Google's Privacy Policy and for the purposes set out above. You can opt out of Google Analytics if you disable or refuse the cookie, disable JavaScript, or use the opt-out service provided by Google.
This site and its owner or representatives may have enabled the Google Analytics Advertising features. Learn more regarding Google Analytics Advertising Features.
We may also use or share interfaces with social media sites such as Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter and others. If you choose to "like" or "share" information from this website through these services, you should review the privacy policy of that service. If you are a member of a social media site, the interfaces may allow the social media site to connect your visits to this site with other Personal Information.
NoticeWhere Bay Area Electric Railroad Association collects Personal Information on the web, we intend to post a purpose statement that explains why Personal Information will be collected and whether we plan to share such Personal Information outside of Bay Area Electric Railroad Association or those working on Bay Area Electric Railroad Association's behalf. Bay Area Electric Railroad Association does not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on Bay Area Electric Railroad Association's behalf unless such transfer is legally required.
ChoiceYou may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to Bay Area Electric Railroad Association. The notice we intend to provide where Bay Area Electric Railroad Association collects Personal Information on the Web should help you to make this choice. If you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you can still visit most of Bay Area Electric Railroad Association's Web sites, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services that involve our interaction with you.
If you chose to have a relationship with Bay Area Electric Railroad Association, such as a contractual or other business relationship or partnership, we will naturally continue to contact you in connection with that business relationship.
SecurityWherever your Personal Information may be held within Bay Area Electric Railroad Association or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the Personal Information that you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure.
Access/AccuracyTo the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, Bay Area Electric Railroad Association wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. Where we collect Personal Information from you on the Web, our goal is to provide a means of contacting Bay Area Electric Railroad Association should you need to update or correct that Information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may send updates and corrections about your Personal Information to This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in your Personal Information that we hold as soon as practicable.
Third Party ServicesThird parties provide certain services available on westernrailwaymuseum.org on Bay Area Electric Railroad Association's behalf. Bay Area Electric Railroad Association may provide information, including Personal Information, that Bay Area Electric Railroad Association collects on the Web to third-party service providers to help us deliver programs, products, information, and services. Service providers are also an important means by which Bay Area Electric Railroad Association maintains its Web site and mailing lists. Bay Area Electric Railroad Association will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third-party service providers are obligated to protect Personal Information on Bay Area Electric Railroad Association's behalf.
Bay Area Electric Railroad Association does not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on Bay Area Electric Railroad Association's behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Similarly, it is against Bay Area Electric Railroad Association's policy to sell Personal Information collected online without consent.
CommitmentWe are committed to privacy and support current industry initiatives to preserve individual privacy rights on the Internet. Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and Bay Area Electric Railroad Association's Web sites are constantly evolving to meet these demands.
If you have any comments or questions regarding our Online Privacy Policy, please contact us at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.. While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as possible.
Your ConsentBy using this Web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to Bay Area Electric Railroad Association's processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above as well as those explained where Bay Area Electric Railroad Association collects Personal Information on the Web. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time.
back to top
Hours
Year RoundSaturdays & Sundays10:30 am – 5:00 pm
Summer Hours(June 13th - August 18th)Wednesdays, Thursdays, Saturdays & Sundays10:30 am to 5:00 pm
Museum Location
5848 State Highway 12Suisun City, CA 94585
(707) 374-2978
Contact Us
Connect
Facebook
Instagram
Yelp
YouTube
Sign Up
Subscribe to our newsletters to receive updates about our activities and events.
Visit / Discover
Plan Your VisitGroup ToursField TripsMuseum Site MapArchivesMuseum StoreCar RosterPassenger CarsStreetcarsInterurban CarsMainline Railroad CarsLight RailLocomotivesElectricSteamDieselFreight CarsMaintenance & Support CarsEventsAbout Us
Railroad HistoryKey SystemSacramento Northern RailwaySan Francisco Municipal RailwayStaffOur Mission and HistoryBlogSupport Us
Make A DonationMembershipVolunteerContact Us
